

Profile

I am with extensive and rich knowledge of all software such as Blockchain, Website, Mobile App and more for over 12 years.

✓ Blockchain Skill

- Smart Contract, DeFi, Ethereum, Solana, Avax, Wax, Algorand, Polygon, BSC, Polkadot
- DApps development; Solidity/Rust + web3.js/ethers.js
- Solidity, Rust, Golang, C++, Java, Python
- Integration with crypto wallets such as Metamask.

✔ Frontend Skill

- HTML5/SCSS/CSS3/SVG/jQuery/JavaScript/BootStrap
- ReactJS/Redux/React Native/Next.js/Gatsby.js
- Vue.js/Nuxt.js/Quasar
- Angular 2,4~13
- Typescript/Web pack
- -Flutter / Android Studio

✓ Backed Skill

- -PHP/JavaSpringJava SpringJavaSpring/ Java/Laravel/Node.js/Python/Rust/Golang/C++
- -SQL and No SQL (MySQL, MYSQL, PostgreSQL, Influx Db, MongoDB), Redis

✓ Tools/Cloud

Firebase/Jenkins/JIRA/Docker/AWS

✓ Version Control System

GitHub/Git Lab/Bit bucket

I have worked on numerous projects from concept to completion. Leads all stages of various technical projects, computer programming and business finance experience.

Be brave. It's never too late to make the world a better place.

Follow me!

✔ Proof of Work

♥ Defi

https://www.goosedefi.com/

https://github.com/Talanted-Blockchain-Dev/goose-defi

♥ Solana game

https://github.com/galaxy-digital/solana-betting-game

https://zankokuarena.io/

Details

Vaughan, L4L 3Y6, Canada +1 505 355 0796 brentjeremynel@gmail.com

NATIONALITY

Thai

DATE / PLACE OF BIRTH

1996.02.05 Thailand

Social Link

- FaceBook
- Twitter
- Gmail
- Skype
- Github
- Linkedin

Skills

REACT

Solidity

Python

Rust

DevOps

Hobbies

FootBall

Languages

English

Thai

♥ Game

https://www.cryptowolf.finance

https://github.com/Talanted-Blockchain-Dev/cryto-wolf-finance

https://casinoastar.com/

https://github.com/Talented-Blockchain-Dev/casino-hilo-main

https://github.com/Talented-Blockchain-Dev/casino-triple-main

https://github.com/Talented-Blockchain-Dev/casino-shootout-main

https://github.com/Talented-Blockchain-Dev/casino-videopoker-main

Employment History

Prolocalize, CTO

AUG, 2019 — PRESENT

This is translation company.

But they translate automatically with AI and python programs.

https://prolocalize.com is our company site.

I am working CTO for this company.

My CEO is Priachat. His telegram id is @topweizhan.

Lucky Shiba, CTO

AUG, 2021 — PRESENT

•This company is in UK and I worked in remote. CEO is Lucas and his telegram id is @iamlucase I worked as CTO for blockchain and game developing Https://Luckyshiba.org This is our product.

Education

Master's Degree, King Mongkut's University of Technology Thonburi

APR. 2013 — MAR. 2018

King Mongkut's Institute of Technology Ladkrabang is a research and educational institution in Thailand. It is situated in Lat Krabang District, Bangkok approximately 30 km east of the city center.

Bangkok Patana School

Apr, 2007 — Mar, 2013

Bangkok Patana School is not just the first British educational institute in Thailand, It has, since its founding, remained one of South East Asia's most respected schools. Offering a wide spectrum of education from Foundation Level all the way up to years 11, 12 and 13. This gives parents confidence that their child is receiving a holistic kind of education. Naturally using the British curriculum, Bangkok Patana School prides itself on supporting its student both in their educational life and other areas of their personal life.

Bangkok Patana School sits in a prime position to offer the very highest quality of education for Thailand's children.